<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EasyToCook</string>

    <string name="logIn_email">Email </string>
    <string name="logIn">Login </string>
    <string name="verify_password">Verify Password </string>
    <string name="signup">Sign UP</string>
    <string name="welcome">Search and Share the Food You Like</string>
    <string name="logIn_passwords">Password</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World</string>
    <string name="next">   Next</string>
    <string name="btn_logOut">Log Out</string>
    <string name="btn_recipeCreation">Create Your Own Recipe</string>
    <string name="Cuisine">Cuisine</string>
    <string name="Ingredient">Ingredient</string>
    <string name="Time">TIme</string>
    <string name="Calories">Calories</string>
    <string name="profile_pic">Profile pic</string>
    <string name="search_dish">Search Dish</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="terms">Agree to Terms and Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="Less_than_half_hour">Less than half hour</string>
    <string name="btw_half_and_one_hour">Between half and 1 hour</string>
    <string name="more_than_a_hour">More than a hour</string>
    <string name="more_than_two_hours">More than 2 hours</string>
    <string name="less_than_500_kcal">Less than 500 Kcal</string>
    <string name="less_than_1K_kcal">Less than 1K kcal</string>
    <string name="btw_1k_and_2k_kcal">Between 1K and 2K kcal</string>
    <string name="more_than_2K">more than 2K kcal</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="cooking_time">Cooking time</string>
    <string name="how_to_cook">How to Cook?</string>
    <string name="save_recipe">Save Recipe</string>
    <string name="type_dish">Search Dish</string>
    <string name="clock_image">Clock Image</string>
    <string name="image_ingredient">ingredient image</string>
    <string name="image_Calories">image calories</string>
    <string name="name_of_receipe">Name of Receipe</string>
    <string name="receipe_detail_cook_time">Cook Time</string>
    <string name="text_view_Caloire">Receipe Detail Calories</string>
    <string name="receipe_detail_instruction">Receipe detail how to cook detail</string>
    <string name="receipe_detail">Receipe Detail</string>
    <string name="receipe_detail_cooking_time">Cooking Time (h):</string>
    <string name="receipe_detail_calories">Calories (Kcal):</string>
    <string name="error">error</string>
    <string name="DishName">Dish Name</string>
    <string name="nextt">next</string>
    <string name="privacy_terms">East to cook App process personal data of their users of services (“Easy to Cook App”) and the visitors of the website easytocook.com (“Website”). In this Privacy Statement, the word “Services” refers jointly to the Website and the App. In this Privacy Statement, the word “User” or “you” refers jointly to our and our group companies’ customers, representatives and other authorized users of our customer organizations, potential customers and the users of the application. Our Privacy Statement explains, for example, the types of personal data we process, how we process the personal data and how you may exercise your rights as a data subject (e.g. right to object, right of access). Some of our services might be subject to a separate privacy policy. If a separate privacy policy applies to a particular service, we will post it in connection with the service in question. This Privacy Statement may be updated from time to time in order to reflect the changes in data processing practices or otherwise. You can find the current version on the Website. We will not make substantial changes to this Privacy Statement or reduce the rights of the Users under this Privacy Statement without providing a notice thereof. 1. DATA CONTROLLER(S) In accordance with the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) Easy to Cook App aims to protect the privacy and use of personal information of all it\'s users including but not limited to citizens and residents of the EU. Easy to Cook App collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Easy to Cook App’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Easy to Cook App \'s users use its application. Easy to Cook App also collects personally identifying information about you when you provide information to us while using our website or application. Where is Your Data Stored? Our servers are located in the U.S.A. This Privacy Statement applies to processing of personal data carried out by Easy to Cook App. Easy to Cook App has appointed a data controlling office responsible for handling all data subject requests and questions relating to the personal data processing of the Easy to Cook App group. 2. PERSONAL DATA PROCESSED AND SOURCES OF DATA The personal data collected and processed by us can be divided into two general data categories: User Data and Analytics Data. User Data User Data is personal data collected directly from you or from our customer organization on behalf of which you are using the services (“Customer Organization”), as the case may be. We may collect User Data from our Users and Customer Organizations in a variety of ways, including, after conclusion of a service agreement with the Customer Organization or when Users register to the services, subscribe to a newsletter or fill out a form. Further, please note that we also collect details of any transactions and payments you carry out through our app and website. User Data that is necessary in order to use the Easy to Cook App The following personal data collected and processed by us is necessary in order for a proper performance of the contract between you and us as well as for our legitimate interest whilst fulfilling our contractual obligations towards our Customer Organizations and for the compliance with our legal obligations. After conclusion of the service agreement between us and the Customer Organization, the Customer Organization provides us with your full name and email address.  When you register to the Easy to Cook App and create a user account, you need to provide us with the following information: full name telephone number email address  information relating to your payment instrument(s) such as the number of your payment instrument(s) and the expiration date of your payment instrument(s) User Data you give us voluntarily Your user or customer experience may be enhanced by providing us with the following information:  Additional Account Information: picture address location data (if you consent to the processing of your location data) other information you provide either when creating a user account or later when modifying your account profile Other Information. We may also process other information provided by you voluntarily such as: information you provide when rating our services marketing opt-ins and opt-outs information you provide by phone or in email or chat correspondence with us, including call recordings of your calls with our customer service  In addition to User Data collected from you and the Customer Organization, we process certain personal data third party service providers provide about you.  If you connect or login to your account with Facebook, Facebook shares with us personal information about you such as your profile picture, a sample of your Facebook friends and your Facebook ID. Same goes for other social media apps, you use along with the Easy to Cook App. Analytics Data Although we do not normally use Analytics Data to identify you as an individual, you can sometimes be recognized from it, either alone or when combined or linked with User Data. In such situations, Analytics Data can also be considered personal data under applicable laws and we will treat such data as personal data. We may automatically collect the following Analytics Data when you visit or interact with Services: Device Information. We collect the following information relating to the technical device you use when using the app: device and device identification number, device IMEI country IP address browser type and version operating system Internet service providers advertising identifier of your device visitor identifier Usage Information. We collect information on your use of the apps, such as: time spent on the application  interaction with other users and the app information on how you use the app the URL of the website you visited before and after you used the app the time and date of your usage the sections of the app you used the products you searched for while using the app Web analytics services The Easy to Cook App use Google Analytics and other web analytics services to compile Analytics Data and reports on visitor usage and to help us improve the services. For an overview of Google Analytics, please visit Google Analytics. It is possible to opt-out of Google Analytics with the following browser add-on tool: Google Analytics opt-out add-on. Advertising and visitor identifiers The Easy to Cook App use pseudonymized identifiers to track and predict your app and service usage and preferences. You can opt-out of the use of these identifiers by changing your operating system settings as follows: Advertising identifiers can be disabled on iOS mobile devices by turning on the Limit Ad Tracking tab (Settings → Privacy → Advertising → Limit Ad Tracking). For an overview and more information on the advertising identifier, please see Apple Advertising and Privacy site. Users identifiers can be disabled on iOS and Android mobile devices by changing your settings. 3. PURPOSES AND LEGITIMATE GROUNDS FOR THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA Purposes There are several purposes of the processing of your personal data by Easy to Cook App: To provide the necessary services and carry out our contractual obligations (legal ground: performance of a contract and legitimate interest) Easy to Cook App processes your personal data to be able to offer the services to you under the contract between you and us or between Customer Organization and us.  We use the data for example to handle your payments or any refunds (where applicable) and to provide our partners (the restaurants and our courier partners) with the information necessary for the preparation or delivery of your order. If you contact our customer service, we will use the information provided by you to answer your questions or solve your complaint.  For our legal obligations (legal ground: compliance with a legal obligation) Easy to Cook App processes data to enable us to administer and fulfil our obligations under law. This includes data processed for complying with our bookkeeping obligations and providing information to relevant authorities such as tax authorities. For claims handling and legal processes (legal ground: legitimate interest) Easy to Cook App may process personal data in relation to claims handling, debt collection and legal processes. We may also process data for the prevention of fraud, misuse of our services and for data, system and network security. For customer communication and marketing (legal ground: legitimate interest) Easy to Cook App processes your personal data to contact you regarding the services and to inform you of changes relating to them. Your personal data are also used for the purposes of marketing the services to you.  For quality improvement and trend analysis (legal ground: legitimate interest) We may also process information about your use of the Easy to Cook App to improve the quality of the services e.g. by analysing any trends in the use of the Easy to Cook App Services. In order to ensure that our services are in line with your needs, personal data can be used for things like customer satisfaction surveys. When possible, we will do this using only aggregated, non-personally identifiable data. Legal grounds for processing Easy to Cook App processes your personal data to perform our contractual obligations towards you or the Customer Organization and to comply with legal obligations. Furthermore, we process your personal data to pursue our legitimate interest to run, maintain and develop our business and to create and maintain customer relationships. When choosing to use your data on the basis of our legitimate interests, we weigh our own interests against your right to privacy and e.g. provide you with easy to use opt-out from our marketing communications and use pseudonymized or non-personally identifiable data when possible. In some parts of the Easy to Cook App Services, you may be requested to grant your consent for the processing of personal data. In this event, you may withdraw your consent at any time. For Users located in Israel:By entering, connecting to, accessing or using the Easy to Cook App Services, you agree and consent to the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Statement, including to the collection, processing, transfer and use of your personal data which is collected as part of the Easy to Cook App Services. If you disagree to any term provided herein, you may not access or use the app. You also acknowledge and confirm that you are not required to provide us with your personal data and that such information is voluntarily provided to us.  4. TRANSFER TO COUNTRIES OUTSIDE EUROPE Easy to Cook App stores your personal data primarily within the European Economic Area. However, we have service providers and operations in several geographical locations. As such, we and our service providers may transfer your personal data to, or access it in, jurisdictions outside the European Economic Area or the User’s domicile.  We will take steps to ensure that the Users’ personal data receives an adequate level of protection in the jurisdictions in which they are processed. We provide adequate protection for the transfers of personal data to countries outside of the European Economic Area through a series of agreements with our service providers based on the Standard Contractual Clauses or through other appropriate safeguards, such as the Privacy Shield Framework.  More information regarding the transfers of personal data may be obtained by contacting us on any of the addresses indicated above.  5. RECIPIENTS We only share your personal data within the organization of Easy to Cook App if and as far as reasonably necessary for the purposes of this Privacy Statement. We do not share your personal data with third parties outside of the organization unless one of the following circumstances applies: For the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement and to authorized service providers To the extent that third parties (such as the restaurants which prepare your order, our courier partners who deliver your order and Customer Organization which may pay your order) need access to personal data in order for us to perform the services, we provide such third parties with your data. Furthermore, we may provide your personal data to our affiliates or to authorized service providers who perform services for us (including data storage, accounting, sales and marketing) to process it for us and to payment service providers to process your payments to us. When data is processed by third parties on behalf of Easy to Cook App, we will take appropriate contractual and organizational measures to ensure that your data are processed exclusively for the purposes specified in this Privacy Statement and in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations and subject to our instructions and appropriate obligations of confidentiality and security measures. Please bear in mind that if you provide personal data directly to a third party, such as through a link on the website, the processing is typically based on their policies and standards. For legal reasons and legal processes We may share your personal data with third parties outside Easy to Cook App if we have a good-faith belief that access to and use of the personal data is reasonably necessary to: (i) meet any applicable law, regulation, and/or court order; (ii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, crime, security or technical issues; and/or (iii) protect the interests, properties or safety of Easy to Cook App, the Users or the public as far as in accordance with the law. When possible, we will inform you about such processing. For other legitimate reasons If Easy to Cook App participates in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we may transfer your personal data to the third party involved. However, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of all personal data. We will give notice to all the Users concerned when the personal data are transferred or become subject to a different privacy statement.  With your explicit consent We may share your personal data with third parties outside Easy to Cook App when we have your explicit consent to do so. You have the right to withdraw this consent at all times free of charge by contacting us. 6. STORAGE PERIOD Easy to Cook App does not store your personal data longer than is legally permitted and necessary for the purposes of providing the services or the relevant parts thereof. The storage period depends on the nature of the information and on the purposes of processing. The maximum period may therefore vary per use. Most personal data relating to a User’s user account with the app will be deleted after a period of 90 days have lapsed after the User has deleted its user account with the Easy to Cook App. Thereafter, a part of the personal data relating to a User’s user account with the Easy to Cook App may be stored only as long as such processing is required by law or is reasonably necessary for our legal obligations or legitimate interests such as claims handling, bookkeeping, internal reporting and reconciliation purposes. All personal data relating to a User’s user account with the Easy to Cook App will be deleted within a period of 10 years after the User has deleted its user account with the Easy to Cook App, with the exception of personal data required in certain rare situations such as legal proceedings. We will store Analytics Data of Users that do not have an account with the Easy to Cook App for a period of 90 days. 7. YOUR RIGHTS Right of access You have the right to access and be informed about your personal data processed by us. We give you the possibility to view certain data through your user account with the Easy to Cook App or request a copy of your personal data. Right to withdraw consent In case the processing is based on a consent granted by the User, the User may withdraw the consent at any time free of charge. Withdrawing a consent may lead to fewer possibilities to use the Easy to Cook App. The withdrawal of consent does not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. Right to rectify You have the right to have incorrect or incomplete personal data we have stored about you corrected or completed by contacting us. You can correct or update some of your personal data through your user account in the Easy to Cook App.  Right to erasure You may also ask us to delete your personal data from our systems. We will comply with such request unless we have a legitimate ground to not delete the data.  Right to object You may have the right to object to certain use of your personal data if such data are processed for other purposes than necessary for the performance of the Easy to Cook App or for compliance with a legal obligation. If you object to the further processing of your personal data, this may lead to fewer possibilities to use the Easy to Cook App. Right to restriction of processing You may request us to restrict processing of personal data for example when your data erasure, rectification or objection requests are pending and/or when we do not have legitimate grounds to process your data. This may however lead to fewer possibilities to use the Easy to Cook App. Right to data portability You have the right to receive the personal data you have provided to us yourself in a structured and commonly used format and to independently transmit those data to a third party. How to use your rights The abovementioned rights may be used by sending a letter or an e-mail to us on the addresses set out above, including the following information: the full name, address, e-mail address and a phone number. We may request the provision of additional information necessary to confirm the identity of the User. We may reject or charge requests that are unreasonably repetitive, excessive or manifestly unfounded.  8. DIRECT MARKETING The User has the right to prohibit us from using the User’s personal data for direct marketing purposes, market research and profiling made for direct marketing purposes by contacting us on the addresses indicated above or by using the functionalities of the Easy to Cook App or the unsubscribe possibility offered in connection with any direct marketing messages. 9. LODGING A COMPLAINT In case the User considers our processing of personal data to be inconsistent with the applicable data protection laws, the User may lodge a complaint with the local supervisory authority for data protection in Finland, the Data Protection Ombudsman (tietosuoja.fi). Alternatively, the User may lodge a complaint with the local supervisory authority for data protection of the User’s country of domicile.  10. INFORMATION SECURITY We use administrative, organizational, technical, and physical safeguards to protect the personal data we collect and process. Measures include for example, where appropriate, encryption, pseudonymization, firewalls, secure facilities and access right systems. Our security controls are designed to maintain an appropriate level of data confidentiality, integrity, availability, resilience and ability to restore the data. We regularly test the Easy to Cook App, systems, and other assets for security vulnerabilities. Should despite of the security measures, a security breach occur that is likely to have negative effects to the privacy of the Users, we will inform the relevant Users and other affected parties, as well as relevant authorities when required by applicable data protection laws, about the breach as soon as possible.</string>
</resources>